zapals.com 2018-12-09

# Privacy Policy - Zapals.com

## YOUR PRIVACY-OUR COMMITMENT TO YOU

Zapals Corporation is committed to safeguarding all information we gather from and about you. Your privacy is not only important to you, but to us as well. The information we gather and how it is used is disclosed in this Privacy Policy. Please review carefully and let us know if you have any questions, concerns or suggestions.

This Privacy Policy applies to the customers and other persons accessing Zapals website (http://www.zapals.com). Unless otherwise stated, customers and other persons who access Zapals website are collectively referred to as "you", "your", "yourself" or "customers", and Zapals Corporation is referred to as "Zapals", "we", "us" and "our".

* * *

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU

### 1\. Personal Information You Provide to Us

Generally, you can browse Zapals.com without giving any Personally Identifiable Information. However, we may ask you to provide further information when you register as a member, make purchases, subscribe to the newsletter, request for product information or services, participate in any online survey or contest, communicate with Zapals' customer service by phone, email or any other way, submit product reviews and more.

Personal Information you provide to us may include a user name and password, email address, full name, phone number, postal address, credit/debit card numbers, expiration data or other billing information (This information is not stored on our server. It is processed directly through the financial institutions). You can choose not to provide us with certain types of information, but doing so may limit your ability to use certain features of Zapals.com. Besides, we may not be able to provide you with certain requested information, products and/or services.

### 2\. Information Collected Automatically

Like many websites on the Internet, we automatically collect certain information about you as you visit and use Zapals website. The automatically gathered data includes, but is not limited to, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type and language, your location, the date and time of your visit, the website's URL that you just came from, which URL you go to next and exit, the number of times you visit each page, and length of visits to certain pages.

We may use the automatically collected information for a number of purposes, such as knowing whether you is logged in or not; which account you are logged in with; recording your browsing histories; storing passwords and form content you have previously entered; analyzing the numbers and frequency of visitors to our website, and the patterns of site use so that we can make the website appealing to as many customers as possible; providing advertising and other information that is relevant to you; and improve our service. Please note that we do not use those automatically collected data to identify you personally.

* * *

## Cookies

A cookie is a small script placed on your computer hard drive by the server of a website that you visit. Generally, we use "cookies" to allow you to enter your password less frequently during a session; keep track of your current shopping session and enable you to proceed to checkout and pay for products; distinguish you from other customers so as to provide information that is targeted to your interests; store information about web pages viewed and advertisements viewed or clicked; collect statistical information about how you use Zapals website so we can improve the way the website works; analyze our web page flow; measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches; improve our products and services; and promote trusty and safety.

Most Internet browsers give you several options to set your preferences regarding cookies. Each browser version works in a slightly different way, but you generally have the ability to accept all cookies, be notified before accepting a cookie, block or restrict cookies from certain sites, or reject all cookies. Please note that certain features of Zapals website will not be available once cookies are disabled.

* * *

## HOW YOUR INFORMATION IS USED AND SHARED

Except as specified in this Privacy Policy, Zapals DOES NOT sell, rent, distribute or lease your personal information to any third party unless we receive your consent or are required by law to do so. We may use personal information that we collect about you for following purposes:

-Create and manage your account

-Contact you about your account

-Verify your identity

-Send a welcoming Email to confirm your username and password

-Communicate with you in response to your inquiries

-Process your order and follow up with your concerns on purchased products

-Provide after-sales services, handle goods returns and recalls

-Periodically send promotional emails about new arrivals, special offers, or other information which we think you may find interesting

-Keep you informed of important functionality changes of Zapals website, updates on our terms and conditions, privacy policy and our new services

-Carry out marketing analysis and research to improve our merchandise selections, customer service and overall shopping experience

-Understand your needs and preferences in an effort to provide customized content and make recommendations based on your past activities

Please note that we may provide your personal information to third parties (e.g. credit card issuers, shippers) who assist us in fulfilling orders placed through our site.

* * *

## HOW WE PROTECT PERSONAL INFORMATION

Zapals takes the security of your personal information very seriously. We have taken a variety of security measures, including information technology security systems, strict access controls and ongoing staff privacy training, to ensure the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We verify your identity before granting access or making changes to your Personally Identifying Information. When you place orders or access your personal information, the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software encrypts all information you put in before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all information, such as your name, postal address, email address, phone number, credit card data, etc. collected on Zapals.com is securely stored within the Zapals controlled database. The database is stored on servers secured behind a firewall. Access to the servers is also passed protected and is strictly limited. **We do not store your credit card details in any way**. They are secured by SSL encryption and directly transmitted to the bank for payment processing. Besides, we continuously communicate our privacy and security guidelines to all Zapals employees and strictly enforce privacy safeguards within the company.

While we use industry-standard precautions to safeguard your personal information, we still cannot guarantee complete security. 100% complete security does not presently exist anywhere online or offline. Besides, you are ultimately responsible for maintaining the privacy of your personal information. **Zapals is not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive your personal information**. Just as importantly, please notify us immediately if you become aware of any unauthorized use of your account or any other breach of security. We will take appropriate actions to protect your privacy and security in the most expeditious manner.

* * *

## CONTROL YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

At Zapals.com, you are provided with certain choices to restrict the collection or use of your Personally Identifiable Information.

You can choose not to provide us with personal information when browsing Zapals.com. Please keep in mind that this may result in restricted access to certain services or the use of certain features of our website. If you have registered as a Zapals member, you can review, update, modify, delete and remove Personally Identifiable Information by signing into your account and visit "My Account". If you encounter any issues or discover any inaccurate information that you are unable to correct, please contact us thru [customerservice@zapals.com](mailto:customerservice@zapals.com).

You also have the right to ask us not to process your personal information for marketing purposes.You can use the "unsubscribe option" at the bottom of every email promotion. You can also send a request to remove you from all marketing email communications via [customerservice@zapals.com](mailto:customerservice@zapals.com). Additionally, you can unsubscribe from receiving the newsletter by visiting "My Account". If at any time, you wish to be completely removed from our database for any reason, simply send us an email with your request via [customerservice@zapals.com](mailto:customerservice@zapals.com).

At this time, the cookies we use do not have an "opt-out" option. However, you still have the option of blocking the use of cookies, as described above, by changing the settings in your Internet browser. Please keep in mind that this may affect your access to certain features or services of our website or that they may not function properly.

* * *

## CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

Protecting everyone's privacy is a top priority at Zapals. We also recognize the importance of protecting children's privacy. Although we sell children's products for purchase by adults. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect Personally Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you believe a chlid under 13 has provided us with any personal information, Please contact us immediately via [customerservice@zapals.com](mailto:customerservice@zapals.com). We will make every effort to delete such personal information as quickly and expeditiously as possible.

* * *

## SCOPE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY: OUTSIDE LINKS

Zapals website may contain links to third-party websites that may collect Personally Identifiable Information about you. **Be aware that Zapals is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other websites.** These sites may have their own privacy policies and statements, which we strongly suggest you review. This Privacy Policy applies only to Zapals website.

* * *

## EFFECTIVE DATE AND MODIFICATIONS

Zapals' Privacy Policy is effective as of the date indicated below. We reserve the right to update, change, modify or otherwise alter this Privacy Policy at any time and without notice. When we change the policy in a material way, a notice will be posted on our website along with the updated Privacy Policy. As such, we encourage you to review our Privacy Policy regularly.

* * *

## CONTACTING US

If you have any questions, concerns or suggestions about Zapals' Privacy Policy or data processing, or if you would like to make a complaint about a possible breach of local privacy laws, please Contact Us thru [customerservice@zapals.com](mailto:customerservice@zapals.com). A customer care member of Zapals Team will endeavor to respond to you within a resonable period of time.

Effective Date of Zapals Privacy Policy: December 29, 2014
